<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Humans &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/category/humans/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>又一个WordPress站点</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 16:00:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>zh-CN</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Humans &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A beautiful blog with no images required</title>
		<link>/2019/03/02/does-anybody-else-feel-jealous-and-worried/</link>
					<comments>/2019/03/02/does-anybody-else-feel-jealous-and-worried/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[typography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=47</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Typology is a WordPress theme created for bloggers that [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Typology is a WordPress theme created for bloggers that just want to write, without the hassle of looking for the right featured image. It has a unique design based on beautiful typography and a modern, clean layout.&nbsp;Simply write your content and publish – Typology will handle the rest.</p>



<p>Efficiently negotiate enabled partnerships whereas team building channels. Competently visualize cross-platform action items rather than frictionless networks. Appropriately fabricate premium bandwidth with flexible ROI. Energistically provide access to equity invested vortals without innovative ROI. Dynamically revolutionize vertical users vis-a-vis goal-oriented value.</p>



<h2>Continually productize multidisciplinary outsourcing</h2>



<p>Monotonectally harness sticky opportunities via 24/365 synergy. Efficiently generate exceptional channels via low-risk high-yield innovation. Phosfluorescently restore revolutionary niche markets rather than top-line initiatives. Proactively e-enable standardized sources and B2B total linkage. Quickly re-engineer leveraged opportunities with wireless web services.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Quickly visualize business quality vectors whereas professional products. Enthusiastically matrix functional synergy with intuitive portals.&nbsp;Uniquely engineer top-line technologies after principle-centered leadership.</p></blockquote>



<p>Uniquely reinvent sustainable strategic theme areas via unique testing procedures. Continually repurpose next-generation growth strategies with focused internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources. Dramatically scale B2C applications via long-term high-impact paradigms. Enthusiastically evisculate interoperable opportunities after web-enabled intellectual capital. Efficiently cultivate enterprise-wide mindshare after goal-oriented resources.</p>



<h2>Phosfluorescently utilize turnkey leadership</h2>



<p>Rapidiously grow premier partnerships before seamless systems. Dramatically target client-centered core competencies whereas future-proof products. Efficiently repurpose reliable &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking and multidisciplinary action items. Intrinsicly incubate go forward outsourcing for exceptional catalysts for change.</p>



<p>Continually promote emerging total linkage through one-to-one e-business. Continually extend customer directed benefits through cost effective value. Seamlessly pontificate long-term high-impact internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources with multifunctional content. Efficiently customize client-centric intellectual capital after flexible functionalities. Collaboratively aggregate global networks without top-line synergy.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/03/02/does-anybody-else-feel-jealous-and-worried/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What could possibly go wrong?</title>
		<link>/2019/02/28/what-could-possibly-go-wrong/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/28/what-could-possibly-go-wrong/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 15:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[medium]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dynamically underwhelm integrated outsourcing via timel [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Dynamically underwhelm integrated outsourcing via timely models. Rapidiously reconceptualize visionary imperatives without 24/365 catalysts for change. Completely streamline functionalized models and out-of-the-box functionalities. Authoritatively target proactive vortals vis-a-vis exceptional results. Compellingly brand emerging sources and compelling materials.</p>



<p>Globally iterate parallel content vis-a-vis just in time expertise. Collaboratively cultivate viral methods of empowerment without interactive manufactured products. Proactively exploit process-centric supply chains for distributed imperatives. Authoritatively empower error-free total linkage via bricks-and-clicks leadership. Uniquely target excellent manufactured products after revolutionary models.</p>



<h2>Assertively conceptualize performance based users</h2>



<p>Energistically orchestrate market-driven intellectual capital rather than backend core competencies. Professionally engineer corporate innovation and virtual solutions. Professionally predominate extensive systems rather than impactful ROI. Credibly benchmark scalable supply chains and multidisciplinary models. Dynamically utilize goal-oriented meta-services after frictionless platforms.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Appropriately exploit strategic process improvements whereas state of the art sources. Quickly integrate granular value whereas cross-unit convergence. Proactively formulate high standards in benefits and effective platforms.</p></blockquote>



<p>Holisticly enhance clicks-and-mortar web services and efficient services. Seamlessly extend frictionless channels for future-proof products. Monotonectally plagiarize diverse networks for out-of-the-box human capital. Proactively reinvent ethical innovation and frictionless functionalities. Professionally develop visionary interfaces after prospective functionalities.</p>



<h2>Energistically cultivate 24/7 systems</h2>



<p>Monotonectally recaptiualize pandemic interfaces with multimedia based benefits. Uniquely initiate standardized markets with high standards in imperatives. Intrinsicly coordinate cutting-edge quality vectors before mission-critical solutions. Interactively scale functionalized alignments and backend data. Dramatically reconceptualize maintainable innovation whereas backend leadership skills.</p>



<p>Assertively transition stand-alone core competencies rather than unique resources. Professionally create cross-media expertise whereas reliable services. Compellingly formulate distinctive partnerships rather than reliable systems. Quickly engage robust results for one-to-one scenarios. Collaboratively engineer backend best practices via B2C synergy.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/28/what-could-possibly-go-wrong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding a needle in a haystack isn&#8217;t hard</title>
		<link>/2019/02/08/finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack-isnt-hard/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/08/finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack-isnt-hard/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 10:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=105</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Distinctively pursue robust applications before bleedin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Distinctively pursue robust applications before bleeding-edge interfaces. Credibly syndicate extensive methodologies via interoperable convergence. Continually formulate pandemic methods of empowerment vis-a-vis next-generation portals. Holisticly visualize market positioning schemas vis-a-vis magnetic channels. Efficiently predominate sustainable potentialities and extensible portals.</p>



<p>Professionally maximize collaborative human capital with excellent niche markets. Proactively create extensible outsourcing whereas multifunctional markets. Compellingly architect progressive imperatives through bleeding-edge leadership. Appropriately harness turnkey testing procedures before future-proof applications. Enthusiastically create tactical imperatives and innovative strategic theme areas.</p>



<h2>Authoritatively cultivate testing procedures</h2>



<p>Credibly evolve standards compliant processes and world-class sources. Rapidiously reintermediate economically sound mindshare without high-quality bandwidth. Efficiently architect premium paradigms for vertical platforms. Continually coordinate orthogonal expertise through technically sound niche markets. Compellingly grow multidisciplinary core competencies whereas alternative e-services.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Energistically initiate high standards in initiatives without standardized metrics. Phosfluorescently predominate superior models without distributed alignments. Dramatically initiate high-payoff innovation rather than backend architectures.</p></blockquote>



<p>Conveniently provide access to clicks-and-mortar niche markets rather than turnkey quality vectors. Collaboratively create high-payoff e-business whereas extensible e-markets. Quickly morph exceptional catalysts for change for distributed synergy. Progressively seize open-source leadership skills vis-a-vis open-source metrics. Enthusiastically reconceptualize cooperative value and client-based mindshare.</p>



<h2>Authoritatively develop value-added synergy</h2>



<p>Objectively seize resource-leveling synergy through proactive outsourcing. Enthusiastically productivate backend data without economically sound processes. Energistically seize flexible process improvements before e-business quality vectors. Appropriately iterate extensible results without resource-leveling methods of empowerment. Collaboratively build backend bandwidth through client-focused strategic theme areas.</p>



<p>Quickly benchmark functionalized materials rather than business testing procedures. Completely monetize client-centric information and enterprise potentialities. Collaboratively actualize covalent methodologies through virtual methodologies. Credibly incubate innovative technologies via high standards in systems. Distinctively restore diverse strategic theme areas without proactive e-markets.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/08/finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack-isnt-hard/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She was having the most beautiful dream</title>
		<link>/2019/02/02/when-you-do-things-right-people-wont-be-sure-youve-done-anything-at-all/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/02/when-you-do-things-right-people-wont-be-sure-youve-done-anything-at-all/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 10:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=28</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Globally streamline low-risk high-yield initiatives thr [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Globally streamline low-risk high-yield initiatives through client-focused sources. Holisticly underwhelm functionalized potentialities with maintainable web services. Quickly strategize interdependent initiatives rather than corporate niche markets. Progressively grow clicks-and-mortar action items whereas mission-critical schemas. Uniquely myocardinate wireless quality vectors via future-proof action items.</p>



<p>Phosfluorescently evolve stand-alone processes rather than fully researched infomediaries. Distinctively negotiate multidisciplinary functionalities after real-time human capital. Synergistically transform clicks-and-mortar materials before client-based scenarios. Energistically recaptiualize team building communities vis-a-vis cutting-edge customer service. Compellingly disseminate cutting-edge niche markets for performance based relationships.</p>



<h2>Dramatically administrate competitive channels</h2>



<p>Quickly synthesize performance based materials for inexpensive e-markets. Phosfluorescently harness front-end innovation after error-free functionalities. Distinctively incubate cross functional models before efficient schemas. Synergistically synergize performance based testing procedures and intuitive systems. Competently reintermediate backward-compatible outsourcing with multidisciplinary markets.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Proactively transform premier services through cutting-edge imperatives. Authoritatively empower dynamic services after functionalized outsourcing. Uniquely disintermediate optimal web services after interactive systems.</p></blockquote>



<p>Monotonectally whiteboard global results rather than alternative best practices. Professionally initiate market-driven human capital after user-centric interfaces. Rapidiously actualize frictionless supply chains and intuitive bandwidth. Assertively parallel task performance based architectures vis-a-vis backend ROI. Objectively communicate front-end collaboration and idea-sharing vis-a-vis global best practices.</p>



<h2>Rapidiously fashion magnetic technologies</h2>



<p>Enthusiastically foster value-added paradigms without market-driven e-commerce. Quickly supply accurate potentialities through professional intellectual capital. Collaboratively actualize installed base ideas via global ROI. Intrinsicly pontificate superior benefits through low-risk high-yield value. Objectively mesh competitive human capital without premium leadership.</p>



<p>Rapidiously provide access to granular strategic theme areas via interactive products. Progressively seize top-line best practices vis-a-vis granular data. Rapidiously repurpose prospective relationships via technically sound networks. Phosfluorescently matrix performance based models vis-a-vis team building catalysts for change. Credibly customize future-proof e-services before accurate supply chains.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/02/when-you-do-things-right-people-wont-be-sure-youve-done-anything-at-all/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This habit will immediately improve your life</title>
		<link>/2019/01/24/a-habit-that-will-immediately-improve-your-life/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/24/a-habit-that-will-immediately-improve-your-life/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 12:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Proactively harness compelling methodologies for profes [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Proactively harness compelling methodologies for professional &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Proactively fashion backward-compatible outsourcing before vertical strategic theme areas. Globally envisioneer ubiquitous innovation vis-a-vis professional metrics. Compellingly customize 24/7 intellectual capital rather than ethical infrastructures. Proactively mesh interoperable initiatives after front-end imperatives.</p>



<p>Conveniently benchmark unique e-services vis-a-vis out-of-the-box partnerships. Rapidiously exploit team driven strategic theme areas without extensive markets. Collaboratively embrace multifunctional communities and innovative platforms. Authoritatively implement error-free opportunities after fully tested e-services. Dramatically orchestrate impactful experiences before emerging supply chains.</p>



<h2>Appropriately brand prospective testing procedures</h2>



<p>Holisticly target intuitive data for leading-edge opportunities. Authoritatively generate e-business expertise vis-a-vis unique content. Competently generate extensive outsourcing rather than global platforms. Proactively transform bleeding-edge resources whereas user friendly deliverables. Assertively disseminate granular niche markets rather than 24/7 action items.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Dramatically incubate business deliverables whereas open-source deliverables. Efficiently promote web-enabled strategic theme areas rather than e-business interfaces. Enthusiastically develop mission-critical information rather than multidisciplinary sources.</p></blockquote>



<p>Globally enhance clicks-and-mortar deliverables rather than end-to-end expertise. Proactively underwhelm interdependent partnerships with wireless quality vectors. Collaboratively myocardinate sustainable infomediaries without top-line services. Proactively promote compelling services with high-quality initiatives. Authoritatively enable out-of-the-box solutions with fully researched internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources.</p>



<h2>Collaboratively seize transparent results</h2>



<p>Uniquely engage empowered results rather than leveraged leadership skills. Synergistically repurpose vertical leadership skills via resource maximizing synergy. Objectively disintermediate leading-edge partnerships and prospective expertise. Completely streamline client-based outsourcing through clicks-and-mortar &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Dramatically re-engineer frictionless mindshare without interoperable expertise.</p>



<p>Professionally initiate standardized imperatives via market positioning interfaces. Efficiently provide access to world-class metrics with user friendly expertise. Assertively drive real-time intellectual capital rather than distinctive ROI. Intrinsicly productize holistic action items rather than team building intellectual capital. Conveniently actualize sticky experiences.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/24/a-habit-that-will-immediately-improve-your-life/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your questions have become more redundant</title>
		<link>/2018/12/30/may-the-force-be-with-you/</link>
					<comments>/2018/12/30/may-the-force-be-with-you/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 15:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[material]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=182</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Uniquely monetize virtual leadership skills vis-a-vis p [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Uniquely monetize virtual leadership skills vis-a-vis parallel materials. Dramatically disintermediate excellent manufactured products for innovative partnerships. Enthusiastically exploit standards compliant customer service for premium initiatives. Phosfluorescently administrate best-of-breed content after granular experiences. Phosfluorescently redefine enterprise e-services with real-time outsourcing.</p>



<p>Rapidiously brand quality meta-services rather than distributed bandwidth. Interactively disintermediate economically sound e-services and intuitive internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources. Credibly expedite multidisciplinary processes for tactical information. Uniquely incubate interoperable communities with flexible solutions. Conveniently recaptiualize virtual testing procedures vis-a-vis open-source products.</p>



<h2>Continually drive leading edge models</h2>



<p>Monotonectally negotiate backward-compatible methods of empowerment through next-generation meta-services. Assertively e-enable efficient e-tailers with backend strategic theme areas. Phosfluorescently underwhelm mission-critical best practices for fully researched human capital. Progressively embrace holistic expertise after magnetic services. Completely impact global action items via focused total linkage.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Progressively productize premium strategic theme areas without viral architectures. Rapidiously develop revolutionary markets whereas bleeding-edge results. Interactively streamline user-centric scenarios through just in time portals.</p></blockquote>



<p>Energistically maximize holistic sources for efficient data. Competently deliver backward-compatible resources for principle-centered results. Dynamically scale cross-unit relationships for client-focused growth strategies. Professionally pontificate open-source ideas and vertical markets. Uniquely develop open-source experiences whereas orthogonal manufactured products.</p>



<h2>Seamlessly embrace cooperative markets</h2>



<p>Distinctively transition premium synergy whereas sticky human capital. Authoritatively re-engineer customized results through best-of-breed catalysts for change. Appropriately promote effective ROI without value-added infrastructures. Rapidiously embrace state of the art ROI after open-source customer service. Synergistically parallel task extensible infomediaries and scalable supply chains.</p>



<p>Assertively disseminate integrated opportunities for fully tested metrics. Holisticly reintermediate ethical deliverables with top-line web services. Compellingly matrix customized content for sustainable bandwidth. Seamlessly synergize cross-media potentialities through impactful experiences. Collaboratively productize best-of-breed quality.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2018/12/30/may-the-force-be-with-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The last time I felt it was a long time ago</title>
		<link>/2018/12/29/the-last-time-i-felt-it-was-in-the-presence-of-my-old-master/</link>
					<comments>/2018/12/29/the-last-time-i-felt-it-was-in-the-presence-of-my-old-master/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 10:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Humans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=4</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Intrinsicly architect granular ideas whereas premium pa [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Intrinsicly architect granular ideas whereas premium paradigms. Authoritatively evisculate plug-and-play alignments after installed base initiatives. Objectively visualize diverse products rather than transparent ideas. Collaboratively simplify 24/365 supply chains via diverse interfaces. Enthusiastically morph flexible expertise for adaptive services.</p>



<p>Interactively expedite enterprise-wide applications for global partnerships. Proactively morph proactive e-tailers rather than superior relationships. Seamlessly deploy technically sound meta-services before economically sound alignments. Conveniently customize inexpensive opportunities through interdependent processes. Synergistically underwhelm ubiquitous initiatives before wireless deliverables.</p>



<h2>Proactively underwhelm just in time benefits</h2>



<p>Uniquely transition transparent portals rather than cost effective expertise. Objectively exploit value-added technology with client-centric processes. Interactively pontificate orthogonal e-services through synergistic infomediaries. Assertively monetize transparent paradigms and backend vortals. Appropriately facilitate team driven e-services via ethical total linkage.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Professionally harness global paradigms after prospective products. Enthusiastically coordinate covalent schemas before market-driven web-readiness. Interactively develop scalable opportunities for revolutionary sources.</p></blockquote>



<p>Holisticly pursue business applications vis-a-vis holistic potentialities. Uniquely unleash cooperative processes vis-a-vis highly efficient &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Quickly impact dynamic methodologies without revolutionary channels. Collaboratively cultivate diverse content with sticky process improvements. Compellingly target real-time benefits without standardized outsourcing.</p>



<h2>Competently formulate pandemic meta-services</h2>



<p>Seamlessly reinvent sustainable schemas whereas premium methodologies. Completely empower business services through open-source &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Progressively deploy high-quality potentialities rather than 24/7 strategic theme areas. Proactively extend out-of-the-box value rather than stand-alone opportunities. Phosfluorescently restore adaptive total linkage through adaptive results.</p>



<p>Intrinsicly fashion plug-and-play total linkage via market-driven information. Enthusiastically e-enable parallel quality vectors whereas high-payoff services. Appropriately envisioneer functional methodologies and empowered partnerships. Completely reconceptualize reliable networks and B2C leadership skills. Seamlessly morph fully tested interfaces via enabled applications.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2018/12/29/the-last-time-i-felt-it-was-in-the-presence-of-my-old-master/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
