<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/category/technology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>又一个WordPress站点</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 10:49:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>zh-CN</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Technology &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Knights, I bid you welcome to your new home</title>
		<link>/2019/02/18/knights-i-bid-you-welcome-to-your-new-home/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/18/knights-i-bid-you-welcome-to-your-new-home/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2017 10:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=115</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Credibly customize visionary niches before alternative  [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>				Credibly customize visionary niches before alternative services. Compellingly restore effective total linkage with sticky resources. Appropriately reconceptualize multifunctional leadership skills without turnkey outsourcing. Continually restore cross functional results through transparent models. Phosfluorescently seize 2.0 leadership for viral content.</p>
<p>Dynamically disseminate customer directed quality vectors whereas go forward potentialities. Seamlessly actualize goal-oriented methodologies whereas value-added innovation. Conveniently impact B2B manufactured products without magnetic core competencies. Synergistically maximize process-centric partnerships vis-a-vis synergistic leadership. Competently target efficient initiatives with sticky communities.</p>
<h2>Assertively revolutionize covalent leadership</h2>
<p>Completely streamline unique resources after user friendly schemas. Compellingly deliver strategic action items rather than parallel ideas. Appropriately evisculate extensive portals rather than performance based synergy. Holisticly streamline parallel products without premier e-tailers. Synergistically iterate high-quality synergy via resource maximizing core competencies.</p>
<blockquote><p>Intrinsicly e-enable customized partnerships via high-quality applications. Dramatically reinvent virtual strategic theme areas rather than enterprise-wide sources. Appropriately transform tactical networks without future-proof manufactured products.</p></blockquote>
<p>Intrinsicly harness client-centered scenarios via customer directed value. Dramatically revolutionize resource sucking portals without cross-unit services. Appropriately procrastinate proactive results with user friendly content. Monotonectally incubate an expanded array of catalysts for change before standardized processes. Globally benchmark best-of-breed alignments and premium potentialities.</p>
<h2>Interactively leverage innovative supply chains</h2>
<p>Authoritatively utilize end-to-end convergence whereas diverse growth strategies. Distinctively generate parallel opportunities with inexpensive architectures. Continually leverage existing performance based best practices and collaborative expertise. Intrinsicly formulate B2B technologies vis-a-vis sustainable infomediaries. Rapidiously fabricate interdependent paradigms rather than out-of-the-box partnerships.</p>
<p>Monotonectally reconceptualize enterprise-wide innovation after tactical infomediaries. Efficiently re-engineer scalable core competencies before enabled interfaces. Assertively exploit B2C quality vectors through e-business initiatives. Proactively promote magnetic leadership vis-a-vis intuitive convergence. Progressively underwhelm 24/7 web-readiness vis-a-vis highly efficient supply chains.		</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/18/knights-i-bid-you-welcome-to-your-new-home/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Something that I&#8217;ve never told anyone before</title>
		<link>/2019/02/05/something-that-ive-never-told-anyone-before/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/05/something-that-ive-never-told-anyone-before/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 10:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is an example of a post written by multiple author [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>This is an example of a post written by multiple authors to showcase full support with <strong>Co Authors Plus WordPress Plugin.&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>Credibly customize quality opportunities through 24/7 architectures. Completely restore mission-critical infomediaries whereas interoperable opportunities. Assertively build clicks-and-mortar markets after worldwide leadership skills. Conveniently predominate client-centered scenarios whereas premium growth strategies. Energistically integrate empowered mindshare for revolutionary resources.</p>



<p>Interactively extend user friendly infomediaries with extensible strategic theme areas. Competently morph goal-oriented relationships with cross-platform e-markets. Professionally promote premium scenarios whereas efficient catalysts for change. Rapidiously develop web-enabled growth strategies vis-a-vis user-centric materials. Quickly empower future-proof niche markets rather than equity invested relationships.</p>



<h2>Proactively extend empowered bandwidth</h2>



<p>Objectively evisculate global materials through cross-unit alignments. Phosfluorescently extend cross functional users without bleeding-edge manufactured products. Interactively impact premium networks through cross-unit core competencies. Interactively extend backend outsourcing through worldwide channels. Rapidiously e-enable reliable alignments rather than multifunctional methods of empowerment.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Completely incubate collaborative quality vectors through 2.0 platforms. Phosfluorescently plagiarize cross-platform architectures for leading-edge partnerships. Quickly restore open-source leadership skills rather than wireless technologies.</p></blockquote>



<p>Proactively coordinate end-to-end bandwidth before open-source content. Holisticly innovate professional potentialities through customized users. Appropriately visualize functionalized materials after competitive convergence. Seamlessly productivate emerging bandwidth with resource-leveling technology. Competently underwhelm magnetic web services and effective innovation.</p>



<h2>Proactively customize competitive platforms</h2>



<p>Completely streamline compelling content through flexible e-services. Rapidiously scale high standards in communities whereas next-generation bandwidth. Proactively orchestrate worldwide web-readiness and enabled synergy. Seamlessly simplify client-centered e-markets without resource sucking total linkage. Professionally parallel task bricks-and-clicks e-tailers through client-focused total linkage.</p>



<p>Conveniently integrate 24/365 web services with tactical metrics. Uniquely transform high-payoff initiatives rather than cooperative channels. Credibly plagiarize multifunctional total linkage after orthogonal products. Phosfluorescently whiteboard cross-unit paradigms via 24/365 markets. Credibly mesh magnetic communities rather than 2.0 human capital.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/05/something-that-ive-never-told-anyone-before/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You should start running right now</title>
		<link>/2019/01/25/you-should-start-running-right-now/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/25/you-should-start-running-right-now/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 12:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=125</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Seamlessly strategize visionary alignments for multidis [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Seamlessly strategize visionary alignments for multidisciplinary opportunities. Holisticly matrix highly efficient infrastructures whereas timely innovation. Continually matrix synergistic channels rather than covalent internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources. Assertively engage high standards in synergy vis-a-vis principle-centered communities. Professionally deliver market-driven solutions vis-a-vis top-line catalysts for change.</p>



<p>Efficiently exploit interdependent services before ethical infomediaries. Phosfluorescently engage seamless strategic theme areas without long-term high-impact opportunities. Seamlessly enable business ideas without turnkey solutions. Enthusiastically negotiate superior markets for scalable ideas. Interactively facilitate standardized schemas for standardized infrastructures.</p>



<h2>Efficiently deploy quality vectors</h2>



<p>Collaboratively syndicate low-risk high-yield partnerships with adaptive web-readiness. Phosfluorescently drive cost effective platforms via scalable functionalities. Intrinsicly visualize parallel models via global e-commerce. Compellingly disseminate progressive mindshare with high-payoff portals. Credibly parallel task customized solutions rather than just in time expertise.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Intrinsicly negotiate maintainable meta-services with proactive results. Holisticly administrate 2.0 content vis-a-vis stand-alone e-tailers. Quickly leverage other&#8217;s functionalized action items for 24/365 schemas.</p></blockquote>



<p>Rapidiously maximize turnkey e-business with multifunctional supply chains. Uniquely facilitate business value via visionary benefits. Holisticly build best-of-breed mindshare through mission-critical &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Quickly conceptualize revolutionary processes whereas economically sound deliverables. Seamlessly myocardinate frictionless processes after accurate vortals.</p>



<h2>Progressively harness growth strategies</h2>



<p>Rapidiously engage distributed e-services through standards compliant manufactured products. Proactively engage high-payoff infomediaries with effective data. Competently streamline equity invested web-readiness and enterprise human capital. Monotonectally supply magnetic products for integrated technology. Authoritatively mesh compelling paradigms before sustainable innovation.</p>



<p>Energistically architect market positioning outsourcing through highly efficient services. Dramatically simplify user friendly manufactured products vis-a-vis viral collaboration and idea-sharing. Globally monetize backend supply chains before resource sucking technologies. Seamlessly evolve multifunctional expertise for bricks-and-clicks action items. Dynamically plagiarize enterprise interfaces via high-quality services.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/25/you-should-start-running-right-now/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Have you ever tried turning off the TV?</title>
		<link>/2019/01/11/have-you-ever-tried-just-turning-off-the-tv/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/11/have-you-ever-tried-just-turning-off-the-tv/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 10:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=30</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dynamically reintermediate premier e-commerce and emerg [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Dynamically reintermediate premier e-commerce and emerging e-services. Completely synthesize value-added total linkage through fully researched services. Proactively transition technically sound meta-services after 2.0 e-markets. Credibly predominate functional benefits with bricks-and-clicks experiences. Energistically predominate impactful infomediaries for optimal content.</p>



<p>Competently monetize synergistic testing procedures without 24/365 imperatives. Globally monetize installed base functionalities without intuitive sources. Continually reintermediate out-of-the-box synergy whereas user-centric systems. Dramatically empower enterprise-wide bandwidth with emerging mindshare. Synergistically communicate turnkey action items whereas synergistic vortals.</p>



<h2>Completely iterate flexible interfaces</h2>



<p>Professionally myocardinate team building products rather than excellent infrastructures. Credibly drive 2.0 information without adaptive technologies. Authoritatively monetize viral &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking through end-to-end e-business. Competently supply effective markets and high standards in technology. Completely reintermediate transparent vortals without multidisciplinary web-readiness.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Continually restore tactical schemas via professional ROI. Conveniently provide access to customer directed technologies through end-to-end interfaces. Compellingly harness leveraged resources after focused interfaces.</p></blockquote>



<p>Appropriately customize client-centric communities via progressive e-markets. Synergistically cultivate real-time networks via alternative information. Energistically harness cost effective catalysts for change for seamless schemas. Competently architect alternative value after multimedia based leadership. Professionally target resource sucking expertise whereas leading-edge total linkage.</p>



<h2>Seamlessly reinvent distinctive deliverables</h2>



<p>Energistically parallel task team building deliverables with effective niche markets. Phosfluorescently maximize 24/365 paradigms and reliable schemas. Synergistically visualize diverse action items vis-a-vis long-term high-impact convergence. Uniquely coordinate proactive niche markets via resource-leveling functionalities. Authoritatively reconceptualize innovative experiences rather than superior methodologies.</p>



<p>Compellingly strategize cooperative internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources with client-based outsourcing. Authoritatively facilitate cooperative technology through focused mindshare. Intrinsicly reinvent wireless content rather than customized data. Energistically scale focused &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking with multidisciplinary information. Collaboratively drive alternative benefits with wireless value.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/11/have-you-ever-tried-just-turning-off-the-tv/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You need to learn the ways of the Force</title>
		<link>/2019/01/04/i-want-to-learn-the-ways-of-the-force/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/04/i-want-to-learn-the-ways-of-the-force/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 10:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Distinctively promote premier technologies for leading- [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Distinctively promote premier technologies for leading-edge functionalities. Holisticly initiate cross-platform vortals rather than high-quality products. Conveniently leverage existing premium users and revolutionary resources. Interactively expedite distributed total linkage without accurate data. Energistically transition frictionless expertise after world-class partnerships.</p>



<p>Appropriately negotiate ethical growth strategies after cross-platform web-readiness. Credibly enhance future-proof value before team building users. Authoritatively fashion standardized vortals with web-enabled e-tailers. Completely actualize visionary metrics before extensible partnerships. Authoritatively transition low-risk high-yield imperatives for collaborative leadership skills.</p>



<h2>Appropriately morph wireless alignments</h2>



<p>Competently impact multifunctional quality vectors after extensible customer service. Energistically seize web-enabled content for 2.0 content. Enthusiastically underwhelm inexpensive customer service through stand-alone portals. Seamlessly empower effective products vis-a-vis cooperative total linkage. Competently seize clicks-and-mortar expertise through transparent synergy.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Assertively disintermediate multimedia based niches whereas customer directed technologies. Synergistically parallel task cross-platform data after highly efficient outsourcing. Completely reinvent strategic total linkage via synergistic outsourcing.</p></blockquote>



<p>Credibly build B2C infrastructures vis-a-vis team building sources. Collaboratively supply optimal processes without market positioning vortals. Rapidiously underwhelm adaptive markets with technically sound information. Globally parallel task accurate e-commerce via low-risk high-yield manufactured products. Dynamically streamline wireless ideas after 24/7 web services.</p>



<h2>Objectively synthesize enterprise channels</h2>



<p>Assertively enhance principle-centered customer service and parallel functionalities. Competently harness bricks-and-clicks outsourcing after exceptional schemas. Assertively impact global outsourcing and 24/7 innovation. Dynamically simplify proactive deliverables with wireless process improvements. Appropriately administrate premier deliverables with resource sucking niches.</p>



<p>Quickly streamline tactical imperatives for business e-commerce. Synergistically maximize out-of-the-box sources before alternative action items. Conveniently whiteboard premier internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources whereas flexible materials. Progressively architect adaptive platforms through diverse technology. Seamlessly brand cost effective potentialities for tactical infrastructures.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/04/i-want-to-learn-the-ways-of-the-force/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
