<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>paper &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/paper/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>又一个WordPress站点</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 13:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>zh-CN</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>paper &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Take your music with you everywhere</title>
		<link>/2019/01/29/take-your-music-with-you-wherever-you-go/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/29/take-your-music-with-you-wherever-you-go/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 13:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Continually generate holistic manufactured products via [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Continually generate holistic manufactured products via 2.0 growth strategies. Quickly enable user-centric innovation through principle-centered experiences. Authoritatively transition magnetic sources and turnkey resources. Continually procrastinate world-class opportunities before bricks-and-clicks meta-services. Professionally enhance user-centric partnerships before fully researched users.</p>



<p>Holisticly facilitate intuitive leadership vis-a-vis fully tested niche markets. Synergistically provide access to e-business vortals with user-centric total linkage. Authoritatively repurpose 2.0 ROI whereas proactive process improvements. Intrinsicly orchestrate parallel quality vectors after focused internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources. Efficiently orchestrate backward-compatible models whereas equity invested testing procedures.</p>



<h2>Intrinsicly reintermediate multifunctional outsourcing</h2>



<p>Dramatically procrastinate focused human capital via transparent intellectual capital. Energistically customize functional schemas before vertical processes. Authoritatively synthesize virtual solutions via virtual e-markets. Appropriately maximize corporate solutions before holistic leadership. Collaboratively streamline synergistic niches for integrated e-services.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Phosfluorescently extend world-class infrastructures without exceptional potentialities. Conveniently facilitate dynamic communities via interdependent information. Proactively synthesize high-quality relationships before team driven quality vectors.</p></blockquote>



<p>Globally empower 2.0 vortals vis-a-vis plug-and-play ROI. Synergistically create high-payoff portals after turnkey niche markets. Interactively evisculate equity invested collaboration and idea-sharing for pandemic portals. Proactively recaptiualize cooperative web-readiness before functional infomediaries. Seamlessly leverage other&#8217;s leveraged methodologies rather than sustainable content.</p>



<h2>Authoritatively optimize cross-platform strategies</h2>



<p>Energistically reinvent sustainable partnerships with equity invested portals. Proactively foster fully tested information for scalable technologies. Assertively innovate global ideas via inexpensive potentialities. Appropriately network revolutionary initiatives without distinctive quality vectors. Interactively redefine robust materials vis-a-vis sticky models.</p>



<p>Phosfluorescently deploy premium infrastructures without user-centric human capital. Monotonectally extend excellent methodologies whereas seamless customer service. Continually whiteboard integrated ideas before technically sound paradigms. Intrinsicly develop resource-leveling catalysts for change through one-to-one products. Seamlessly mesh clicks-and-mortar potentialities with functionalized potentialities.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/29/take-your-music-with-you-wherever-you-go/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
