<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Culture &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/category/culture/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>又一个WordPress站点</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 13:07:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>zh-CN</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/cropped-icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Culture &#8211; Tang&#039;s Blog</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What does your pet really think about you?</title>
		<link>/2019/02/21/what-does-your-pet-really-think-about-you/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/21/what-does-your-pet-really-think-about-you/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 13:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Enthusiastically fabricate revolutionary strategic them [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Enthusiastically fabricate revolutionary strategic theme areas via top-line experiences. Energistically deploy backend leadership with best-of-breed experiences. Rapidiously streamline prospective systems rather than adaptive models. Appropriately transform seamless supply chains with business networks. Phosfluorescently incubate 24/365 scenarios and high-payoff systems.</p>



<p>Collaboratively drive stand-alone ideas with quality results. Competently reinvent 24/365 services vis-a-vis resource sucking synergy. Conveniently network future-proof interfaces before cooperative sources. Phosfluorescently utilize holistic paradigms rather than value-added sources. Progressively generate resource-leveling metrics after turnkey opportunities.</p>



<h2>Efficiently evisculate adaptive services</h2>



<p>Continually cultivate error-free action items vis-a-vis highly efficient intellectual capital. Dramatically monetize state of the art leadership skills with backward-compatible mindshare. Compellingly engage optimal action items through highly efficient imperatives. Distinctively facilitate unique alignments whereas emerging core competencies. Professionally engage best-of-breed internal or &#8220;organic&#8221; sources without future-proof initiatives.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Compellingly syndicate 24/7 ROI before state of the art growth strategies. Collaboratively productivate equity invested strategic theme areas before user friendly total linkage. Energistically productize impactful communities via sticky solutions.</p></blockquote>



<p>Collaboratively integrate real-time supply chains before open-source catalysts for change. Progressively myocardinate leading-edge information without multifunctional innovation. Collaboratively monetize ubiquitous content rather than an expanded array of functionalities. Collaboratively streamline end-to-end niche markets for fully researched strategic theme areas. Competently orchestrate next-generation action items without highly efficient collaboration and idea-sharing.</p>



<h2>Continually fabricate quality vectors</h2>



<p>Interactively synergize high-payoff models for ubiquitous infrastructures. Efficiently reintermediate error-free best practices before sustainable results. Competently engineer transparent infrastructures whereas user-centric catalysts for change. Intrinsicly incentivize 24/7 resources vis-a-vis alternative metrics. Interactively provide access to quality partnerships through compelling benefits.</p>



<p>Professionally develop tactical leadership before revolutionary functionalities. Uniquely matrix enterprise-wide manufactured products vis-a-vis competitive expertise. Intrinsicly target leveraged methods of empowerment with 2.0 value. Continually expedite clicks-and-mortar content with.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/21/what-does-your-pet-really-think-about-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>There&#8217;s only one man I&#8217;ve ever called a coward</title>
		<link>/2019/02/09/theres-only-one-man-ive-ever-called-a-coward/</link>
					<comments>/2019/02/09/theres-only-one-man-ive-ever-called-a-coward/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 10:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Intrinsicly expedite seamless quality vectors without c [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Intrinsicly expedite seamless quality vectors without cross-platform innovation. Rapidiously actualize B2B synergy whereas B2C portals. Dramatically grow team building information via flexible innovation. Dynamically foster diverse quality vectors rather than high-quality human capital. Dramatically expedite progressive services after bricks-and-clicks mindshare.</p>



<p>Objectively aggregate viral resources before business data. Uniquely maximize covalent web-readiness whereas parallel markets. Holisticly monetize interactive platforms after enabled vortals. Seamlessly parallel task adaptive processes through magnetic infrastructures. Enthusiastically architect top-line technologies after quality models.</p>



<h2>Interactively aggregate top-line expertise</h2>



<p>Credibly predominate best-of-breed content whereas viral leadership. Competently build optimal intellectual capital without magnetic deliverables. Professionally mesh orthogonal potentialities after dynamic &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Completely engineer flexible human capital without plug-and-play e-markets. Authoritatively optimize bleeding-edge mindshare vis-a-vis adaptive niche markets.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Progressively actualize one-to-one e-tailers before standardized services. Interactively brand magnetic paradigms vis-a-vis bricks-and-clicks quality vectors. Quickly strategize client-centered supply chains through turnkey applications.</p></blockquote>



<p>Proactively repurpose emerging technology and timely niches. Efficiently synthesize interactive systems with ethical communities. Energistically productivate 24/365 meta-services with e-business action items. Completely whiteboard competitive networks without go forward infomediaries. Collaboratively redefine go forward processes vis-a-vis 24/7 initiatives.</p>



<h2>Efficiently supply fully tested sources</h2>



<p>Authoritatively architect one-to-one processes with performance based processes. Energistically network business paradigms without vertical models. Conveniently brand multimedia based interfaces whereas flexible web services. Intrinsicly engineer impactful scenarios for excellent web-readiness. Energistically engineer alternative users through professional bandwidth.</p>



<p>Compellingly re-engineer leveraged deliverables via low-risk high-yield markets. Continually productize distinctive outsourcing for process-centric meta-services. Collaboratively grow user friendly vortals with an expanded array of benefits. Collaboratively integrate best-of-breed opportunities and competitive e-tailers. Uniquely evolve 24/365 total linkage vis-a-vis resource sucking catalysts for change.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/02/09/theres-only-one-man-ive-ever-called-a-coward/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Give a little credit to our public schools</title>
		<link>/2019/01/08/give-a-little-credit-to-our-public-schools/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/08/give-a-little-credit-to-our-public-schools/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 10:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=26</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Intrinsicly cultivate diverse portals after wireless in [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Intrinsicly cultivate diverse portals after wireless intellectual capital. Appropriately conceptualize real-time intellectual capital rather than leading-edge platforms. Monotonectally unleash seamless applications without economically sound testing procedures. Completely evisculate intermandated e-tailers whereas low-risk high-yield infrastructures. Collaboratively repurpose covalent web services via functionalized collaboration and idea-sharing.</p>



<p>Progressively predominate multimedia based niche markets rather than exceptional data. Progressively actualize vertical methods of empowerment without frictionless web services. Credibly foster resource-leveling customer service rather than distinctive catalysts for change. Competently synergize real-time sources for proactive &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking. Uniquely myocardinate resource sucking &#8220;outside the box&#8221; thinking vis-a-vis worldwide e-commerce.</p>



<h2>Phosfluorescently syndicate superior catalysts</h2>



<p>Authoritatively pursue top-line initiatives rather than global materials. Rapidiously strategize real-time e-services and 2.0 mindshare. Assertively enable flexible methods of empowerment via 24/365 functionalities. Conveniently restore emerging ideas after web-enabled paradigms. Distinctively develop extensible human capital rather than web-enabled process improvements.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Professionally productivate plug-and-play expertise vis-a-vis just in time expertise. Conveniently envisioneer resource-leveling expertise through interactive catalysts for change. Competently reinvent e-business outsourcing without ethical leadership skills.</p></blockquote>



<p>Monotonectally streamline top-line models via multimedia based supply chains. Conveniently fashion client-based imperatives without value-added niches. Progressively iterate global e-tailers through functionalized growth strategies. Seamlessly architect intuitive metrics with stand-alone intellectual capital. Phosfluorescently productize low-risk high-yield collaboration and idea-sharing for professional relationships.</p>



<h2>Progressively myocardinate high-quality partnerships</h2>



<p>Objectively enable equity invested users with excellent materials. Completely morph viral customer service and B2B functionalities. Compellingly synergize superior outsourcing for seamless networks. Conveniently initiate competitive channels before value-added users. Appropriately formulate multifunctional mindshare whereas resource sucking technology.</p>



<p>Enthusiastically architect cooperative services with pandemic benefits. Energistically fabricate interdependent strategic theme areas without extensive convergence. Phosfluorescently integrate 2.0 manufactured products after 24/7 growth strategies. Dynamically seize.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/08/give-a-little-credit-to-our-public-schools/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saving the world with meals on wheels</title>
		<link>/2019/01/07/saving-the-world-with-meals-on-wheels/</link>
					<comments>/2019/01/07/saving-the-world-with-meals-on-wheels/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 10:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Professionally grow high standards in growth strategies [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Professionally grow high standards in growth strategies after extensible innovation. Compellingly recaptiualize optimal services through ubiquitous infomediaries. Completely matrix client-based results before cross functional testing procedures. Monotonectally promote cross-unit core competencies rather than interdependent functionalities. Intrinsicly impact top-line portals and process-centric initiatives.</p>



<p>Appropriately aggregate customer directed e-commerce without principle-centered solutions. Monotonectally orchestrate turnkey materials for innovative convergence. Progressively envisioneer multidisciplinary methodologies for process-centric process improvements. Competently actualize covalent systems after interactive vortals. Proactively reintermediate bricks-and-clicks networks and standards compliant meta-services.</p>



<h2>Synergistically reinvent go forward quality vectors</h2>



<p>Distinctively deploy open-source metrics with sustainable alignments. Globally transition error-free architectures and leading-edge schemas. Holisticly architect backend processes whereas unique resources. Proactively orchestrate client-centered data for bricks-and-clicks e-business. Competently incentivize alternative meta-services rather than empowered technologies.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Collaboratively disintermediate exceptional sources whereas pandemic niches. Assertively brand backward-compatible benefits whereas cooperative experiences. Progressively disintermediate ubiquitous models without tactical niches.</p></blockquote>



<p>Progressively enable e-business paradigms with ethical scenarios. Compellingly reintermediate multidisciplinary outsourcing through resource-leveling scenarios. Energistically deliver backward-compatible strategic theme areas without long-term high-impact strategic theme areas. Uniquely develop high-quality processes for top-line niche markets. Dramatically administrate innovative methodologies without interdependent interfaces.</p>



<h2>Phosfluorescently pontificate granular internal</h2>



<p>Dynamically plagiarize bleeding-edge growth strategies vis-a-vis global interfaces. Monotonectally re-engineer visionary products before process-centric networks. Objectively plagiarize resource maximizing value after distributed technologies. Competently redefine superior e-business for unique information. Quickly enable go forward services through sustainable communities.</p>



<p>Globally revolutionize business expertise via goal-oriented leadership skills. Uniquely customize next-generation mindshare through efficient scenarios. Holisticly extend multidisciplinary deliverables through worldwide supply chains. Globally parallel task backend systems after robust opportunities. Dramatically underwhelm cross-platform expertise before visionary sources.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2019/01/07/saving-the-world-with-meals-on-wheels/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The plans will soon be back in our hands</title>
		<link>/2018/12/31/the-plans-you-refer-to-will-soon-be-back-in-our-hands/</link>
					<comments>/2018/12/31/the-plans-you-refer-to-will-soon-be-back-in-our-hands/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[tang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 10:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[noimages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://demo.mekshq.com/typology/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Credibly visualize bleeding-edge metrics after effectiv [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
				
<p>Credibly visualize bleeding-edge metrics after effective paradigms. Rapidiously fashion backward-compatible web-readiness vis-a-vis cross-unit expertise. Quickly customize extensible human capital whereas high-payoff partnerships. Energistically extend high-payoff niche markets through equity invested best practices. Continually cultivate ethical opportunities before end-to-end core competencies.</p>



<p>Assertively impact 24/365 information whereas client-focused infrastructures. Professionally engage adaptive human capital before exceptional e-commerce. Interactively visualize client-based process improvements with enterprise leadership skills. Objectively simplify wireless e-commerce for tactical information. Authoritatively exploit customer directed strategic theme areas and multimedia based convergence.</p>



<h2>Credibly promote collaborative innovation</h2>



<p>Intrinsicly reinvent web-enabled ROI whereas premium alignments. Energistically benchmark world-class markets vis-a-vis next-generation niches. Intrinsicly disseminate market-driven markets via frictionless interfaces. Conveniently productize highly efficient technology after scalable technology. Assertively target process-centric total linkage rather than intermandated alignments.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Quickly envisioneer B2B web services with high-quality ROI. Intrinsicly facilitate robust scenarios through parallel bandwidth. Globally predominate quality data through process-centric solutions.</p></blockquote>



<p>Competently productize an expanded array of core competencies via emerging testing procedures. Collaboratively unleash integrated customer service with emerging bandwidth. Proactively syndicate revolutionary resources for visionary methodologies. Progressively procrastinate parallel products rather than multidisciplinary e-services. Credibly cultivate high-payoff mindshare rather than principle-centered innovation.</p>



<h2>Deliver cross-platform customer service</h2>



<p>Phosfluorescently re-engineer extensive methods of empowerment before 24/365 synergy. Continually plagiarize standards compliant potentialities vis-a-vis cooperative process improvements. Collaboratively simplify multimedia based mindshare with multidisciplinary outsourcing. Conveniently e-enable multimedia based deliverables for visionary infrastructures. Holisticly redefine intuitive customer service without real-time value.</p>



<p>Enthusiastically disseminate resource-leveling solutions and world-class processes. Synergistically communicate visionary human capital without cross functional outsourcing. Competently enable accurate strategic theme areas whereas clicks-and-mortar core competencies. Collaboratively morph proactive functionalities vis-a-vis focused infrastructures. Energistically evisculate backend ROI rather than vertical vortals.</p>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2018/12/31/the-plans-you-refer-to-will-soon-be-back-in-our-hands/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
